mailtrack.io 2014-03-30

# Privacy Policy — MailTrackMailTrack

### PRIVACY POLICY

1.- In compliance of the Spanish Law 15/99, as of December 13, of personal data protection, you are hereby informed that all the personal data that you provide us with through the website [mailtrack.io](http://mailtrack.io/) or any web page or website associated to the foregoing, will be processed in a file owned by THE MAIL TRACK COMPANY, S.L (hereinafter MAIL TRACK ), owner of the abovementioned website, with corporate domicile in Barcelona (Spain), Córcega nº 301, Planta ático, puerta 1. 08008, Barcelona (España) and NIF B66095670. This file, which has been registered before the Spanish Data Protection Agency, has been created with the purpose of providing the services and inform you about products and services.

2.- You can exercise you rights to access, rectify, erase and object the processing of your personal data at any time by sending a writing request to MAIL TRACK’s abovementioned address or to the following e-mail address: [hi@mailtrack.io](mailto:hi@mailtrack.io).

3\. In order to properly attend your request, please attach all your personal data (name, surname, postal address, telephone, e-mail address and any other contact detail that we can use to verify your identity and contact you) and a copy of you ID card or a photo-ID. All our communications with you will be delivered with the highest available reserve and confidentiality levels. Your personal data will be duly and diligently processed, in accordance with the provisions set forth in the Spanish laws; nevertheless, if you decide to publish any information or send a public message to our website, it will be executed accordingly.

4.- We undertake to take all the security measures that we deed necessary to warrant the security and privacy or your personal data.

5.- Our services may eventually use cookies to provide you with the best possible user experience when using our website. Cookies are small storage devices that are installed in your computer’s hard drive and can be used to optimize the performance of our services. You can modify or block our cookies at any time, although in this case your user experience may be affected. Please read through our COOKIES section for further information Cookies policy.

Cookies help us deliver our services. By using our services, you agree to our use of cookies. OK Learn more
